'Transform Town' ability is avaliable for heros starting from level 10.<br>
Ability rebuilds the town and converts it into Hero's race. Only standard buildings and dwellings will be rebuilt. Magic Guild rebuilds up to level 2. All unbought dwelling creatures of town's original race will be lost.<br>Town garrison must be empty.<br><br> Cost: 25000 Gold, 15 Wood, 15 Ore, 5 Mercury, 5 Crystals, 5 Sulfur, 5 Gems 