Disir are mysterious creatures who often act as protective spirits of Norse Clans. The legends say their bodies are formed from the ashes, scattered from the burial pyres of fallen dwarven warriors, and Arkath himself breathed life into them. They are worshiped together with the fallen warriors and clan ancestors on celebrations called Disablot which are holded regularly across Dwarven settlements.